Hi guys welcome back to my channel today we will talk
about ICICI Lombard share
you will see that it has created an inverter hammer
pattern today and in this you will
see that it has bridged both its 10m and 20m today
so it means that
somewhere or the other buyers have become active in it today
and its target can come out from here
now its first
target of 1956 can be hit and if
this share starts moving above this then almost from
here it
can show you the price of 2000 from here if
it breaks out this level of 1956 then you
will see almost the second pattern will be
created from here b1 and the pattern of beat will be
created from here and almost
if buyers become active in it then almost
its movement will be very
great, it may
even go above 2000 from here
and if we exaggerate a bit then we will stop
short of this for once  Let's assume that if it
breaks out of 56 then you will get a lump of 2000,
you will get a lump movement of 50 points. Okay, secondly,
for confirmation, if you look at it,
we use the RSE indicator. In this,
we will see
that the stock should move within this blue line,
which is a light blue line.
If it crosses above it, then it is even
better. You will see that if it
crossed below, then it was almost around
872. You had a buying
opportunity here.
Now, if it crosses above 1956, then it can
go almost to around 70. If it crosses above it, then the
stock can go to around 2000.
Then here we also use another indicator, the
buzzer band. If
we see according to this, then it will see that it has
broken out today, the yellow line of the indicator, so almost
see from here.
According to the indicator, the almost target of 1955
is showing, from here it is fine, please like the video,
if you are new to the channel then
please subscribe to the channel.